banknetindia.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy

Banknetindia.com is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We aim to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the Banknetindia.com and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion. 

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in India . The information we gather on Banknetindia.com may be shared within the affiliated companies of the Bnet India group on a worldwide basis and also used to undertake analysis of our database such as aggregate profiling of our registered users. 

Banknetindia.com contain links to other Web sites and third party advertisements over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

Banknetindia.com contain links to other Web sites and third party advertisements over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. For this, you can click on the relevant provider's website in the list below. Currently, the following third parties are syndicating ads on Banknetindia.com: 

Google AdSense (www.google.com)  
DoubleClick DFA/Rich Media (www.doubleclick.com)   
Mediaplex/ValueClick (www.mediaplex.com)  
Eyeblaster (www.eyeblaster.com)   
EyeWonder (www.eyewonder.com)   
Interpolls (www.interpolls.com)   
Pointroll (www.pointroll.com)   
Unicast (www.unicast.com)   
Dynamic Logic/Safecount (www.safecount.net)   
Factor TG (www.factortg.com)   
IAG (www.iagr.com)   
InsightExpress (www.insightexpress.com)   
Tyroo (www.tyroo.com)  
Komli (www.komli.com)

Please note that above may not be complete list. Also at our sole discretion, we reserve the right to change this vendors list at any time. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Information**

In some areas of Banknetindia.com, we request or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, contact information, and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In other areas, we collect or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your code, age, preferences, gender, interests and favourites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. 

We use cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve the quality of our services. 

Our servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

**Our Use of Your Information**

We use the information we gather on Banknetindia.com, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the Banknetindia.com, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that affiliated companies offer. 

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 

We may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from us or our affiliated companies or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail, newsletter or other communications. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. 

We have areas on Banknetindia.com where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in these areas becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or to contact you for further information. 

We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

As our organization, membership and services evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes, where applicable. We therefore reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect. 

If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to email us at info@banknetindia.com 

**Contact Information**

Banknetindia.com is part of BNet India Pvt. Ltd., a Mumbai, India based private limited company with its principal place of business at 57, 2nd Floor, Juhu Supreme Centre, Gulmohar Cross Road No 9, Juhu Scheme, Mumbai 400049, India. BNet India Pvt. Ltd. is the legal entity which determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at the Banknet India Site. 

Thank you for using Banknetindia.com. 

Go back to our home page.
